okay let's look at the solution for our
computer architecture quiz
the question was what computer
architecture is about is it about
building faster transistors it is not
computer architecture is about maybe
finding how to use these faster
transistors to build better computers in
some way is it about how to build faster
computers it is one of the possibilities
for how computers can be better if
they're faster so if we need a faster
computer computer architecture is
definitely about how to do that how to
build larger buildings this is not
correct how to design energy-efficient
computers again energy efficiency if
that is what we're after is a way of
improving computers so we definitely are
interested in that in computer
architecture how to build buildings that
fit more computers this again is about
buildings not about building computers
so this is not true and how to build
computers that fit better into buildings
is about building computers that are
more suited for some purpose in this
case fitting more of them into buildings
so computer architects might be worried
about this